Guide to the Ray Benson Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2018-078, 12 Linear Feet
  - Letter from Mayor, David T. Clark, from the town of Paw Paw about the Paw Paw Homecoming Benefit Concert that Asleep at the Wheel participated in; the letter was originally framed by Harry & Pat Knock, January 6, 1983-July 18, 1984 (Box 2811, Folder 22)
  - Austin City Limits Hall of Fame Inductee award for Asleep at the Wheel, 2 red and blue city outlines, 2015 (Box 2812, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Recording Arts & Sciences award for Asleep at the Wheel for Best Country Instrumental Performance, a gold phonograph on wood stand, 1987 (Box 2812, Folder 2)
  - Americana Music Association's Lifetime Achievement for Performance for Asleep at the Wheel, a hand painted guitar award, 2009 (Box 2812, Folder 3)
  - Ray Benson's black cowboy hat made by Lariat Ranchwear in Austin, Texas, especially made for Benson, undated (Box 2813, Item 1)
  - Framed album covers such as The Wheel Keeps On, The Wheel Goes On, and Tribute to the Music of Bob Wills and the Texas Playboys, including photo of Asleep at the Wheel performing, undated (Box 2814, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Appreciation from the Country Music Association to Asleep at the Wheel and Lifetime Achievement Award from Texas Dance Hall Preservation to Benson, October 26, 2017 (Box 2814, Folder 2)
  - Asleep at the Wheel's Keepin' Me Up Nights and Western Standard Time, including Comin' Right at Ya book covers, 1990-2015 (Box 2814, Folder 3)
  - Concert posters for Asleep at the Wheel's 25th Anniversary Reunion Tour, A Ride with Bob from Austin to Tulsa, and others, 2006-2015 (Box 2814, Folder 4)
  - Discoveries: For Record and CD Collectors on Bob Wills, Issue 124, September 1998 (Box 2814, Folder 5)
  - Billboard magazine and Vintage Guitar magazine, 2007-2013 (Box 2814, Folder 6)
  - News clippings about Asleep at the Wheel from Ruidoso Free Press, Austin American-Statesman, The Washington Post, and Austin Chronicle, 1988-2011 (Box 2814, Folder 7)
  - Black, white, and red shirt that Benson wore on stage often, undated (Box 2815, Item 1)
  - Guitar case & Guitar, "Woodie", in case that Benson has played for the past 20 years, undated
  - Austin Music Awards, Twentieth Anniversary Show poster signed by Benson, Lyle Lovett, Johnny Smith, and others, 26.25"x20.25", 2002 (Frame 1, Item Annex B)
  - Framed gift to Asleep at the Wheel for "Congratulations on Twenty-Five Years of Keeping the Wheel Rollin'" from Capitol Nashville, 25.5"x23.5", September 22, 1995 (Frame 2, Item Annex B)
  - Signed poster for Fire Relief: The Concert for Central Texas, signed by Lyle Lovett, Dixie Chicks, Augie Meyers, and Benson, undated (Map-case Dr. 4, Item 1)
  - Asleep at the Wheel Remembers The Alamo poster, undated (Map-case Dr. 4, Item 2)
  - Fathers and Sons by Bob Wills and his Texas Playboys and Asleep at the Wheel, large cover design, 1974 (Map-case Dr. 4, Item 3)
- Accession 2019-128, 8 Linear Feet 2 posters
  Archival materials donated by Ray Benson, lead singer of the iconic Western Swing band Asleep at the Wheel dating 1972-2018. Additions to this archive include awards, articles and press clippings pertaining to Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel from national and international newspapers and magazines both print and online, press kit materials, photographs, tour itineraries, celebrity endorsements by Ray Benson and ephemera. The majority of press includes Asleep at the Wheel album reviews including 10, Asleep at the Wheel Tribute to the Music of Bob Wills and the Texas Playboys, and Asleep at the Wheel Remembers the Alamo, Grammy, CMA, and BMI nominations and awards for Asleep at the Wheel, AATW Billboard album and single chart positions, movie reviews of Wild Texas Rose co-starring Dolly Parton, Ray Benson and Gary Busey, and reviews of A Ride With Bob: From Austin to Tulsa, A Musical Drama About the Life and Legend of Bob Wills written by Ann Rapp and Ray Benson and starring Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel. Ephemera includes Ray Benson's childhood passport, his chauffeur license and date books, concert posters and record flats.
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, Austin Music Awards, Hall of Fame Winner, Ray Benson, 2001-2002 (Box 3330, Folder 1)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards Best Country Band Asleep at the Wheel, 2005-2006 (Box 3330, Folder 2)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards Best Country Band Asleep at the Wheel, 2005-2006 (Box 3330, Folder 3)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards Country award, Asleep at the Wheel, 2006-2007 (Box 3330, Folder 4)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards Band of the Year award, Asleep at the Wheel, 2006-2007 (Box 3330, Folder 5)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards 2011-2012, Bismeaux Records Best Local label award, March 13-18, 2012 (Box 3330, Folder 6)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle and SXSW Austin Music Awards 2012-2013, Bismeaux Records Best Local label award, March 12-17, 2013 (Box 3330, Folder 7)
  - "Ray Benson Asleep at the Wheel"; Award plaque, The Austin Chronicle, SXSW & Cap Metro Mobile App present The 32nd Annual Austin Music Awards Bismeaux Records Best Local label award, 2013-2014 (Box 3330, Folder 8)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Nomination plaque, The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences certificate nominating Asleep at the Wheel's song "Fat Boy Rag" for the "Best Country Instrumental Performance" award signed by Jay L. Cooper, National President of NARAS, 1975 (Box 3330, Folder 9)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Nomination plaque, The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences certificate nominating Asleep at the Wheel's song "Route 66" for the "Best Country Vocal Performance by a Duo or Group" award, signed by Jay L. Cooper, National President of NARAS, 1976 (Box 3330, Folder 10)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Nomination plaque, The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences certificate nominating Asleep at the Wheel's song "The Wheel" album for the "Best Country Vocal Performance by a Duo or Group" award, signed by Jay L. Cooper, National President of NARAS, 1977 (Box 3330, Folder 11)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Nomination plaque, The National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences certificate nominating Asleep at the Wheel's song "Ragtime Annie" for the "Best Country Instrumental Performance" award, signed by J. William Denny, National President of NARAS, 1977 (Box 3330, Folder 12)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Certificate of appreciation presented to Ray Benson for his album production contribution of Texas Top Hand, # 1 Country Album, 1997 N.A.I.D. Award Winners (Box 3330, Folder 13)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Ray Benson's membership certificate, Memphis Chapter, National Academy of Recording Arts & Sciences, July 19, 1988 (Box 3330, Folder 14)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Ray Benson's Honorary Texas Citizen certificate, signed "The Texas Playboys Leon Rausch", March 6, 2005 (Box 3330, Folder 15)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Award, 13th Annual The Austin Chronicle Austin Music Awards Hall of Fame, winner: Ray Benson, 1994-1995 (Box 3330, Folder 16)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Music Row: Nashville's Entertainment Industry Newspaper, Volume 7, #5 Asleep at the Wheel on cover, March 19, 1987 (Box 3330, Folder 17)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Program for the BMI Awards Thirty Second Annual Awards dinner, June 19, 1984 (Box 3330, Folder 18)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; 1989 Governors Award Celebration invitation, Nashville Chapter of the National Academy of Recording Arts and Science honoring Willie Nelson, June 20, 1989 (Box 3330, Folder 19)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; MCA industry release for Asleep at the Wheel's Framed album, Ray Benson's signature on back of 2nd page, undated (Box 3330, Folder 20)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Cartoon drawing, Asleep at the Wheel with Ray Benson caricature inscribed "Ray thought you'd want this" signed [Mark (?)], 1998 (Box 3330, Folder 21)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; As The Wheel Turns-Spring 2000, television highlights and merchandise order form, page 3-4 from the official fan club newsletter (Box 3330, Folder 22)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Tri-fold mailer announcing "The Best of Austin City Limits: Country Music's Finest Hour music compilation on Epic/Legacy Records, including Asleep at the Wheel, addressed to Mrs. Maury Seifert, September 23, 1996 (Box 3330, Folder 23)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Sony Music release flyer for Asleep at the Wheel's live album "Back to the Future Now: Live at Arizona Charlie's, Las Vegas, Lucky Dog Records (Box 3330, Folder 24)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Oversized postcard "Greetings from Asleep at the Wheel" announcing Asleep at the Wheel's Silver Anniversary event at Bass Music Hall, Austin, Texas, September 23, 1995 (Box 3330, Folder 25)
  - "Old Press 1972-1997"; Newspaper clippings featuring Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel, various news outlets, 1987, 1990, 2000-2001, undated (Box 3330, Folder 26)
  - "Press No Date"; Magazine articles, trade press and newspaper clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson, undated (Box 3330, Folder 27)
  - "Discography"; Asleep at the Wheel discography and Ray Benson's resume' with post-it note inscribed with "75 copies collated Master", 1972-1994 (Box 3331, Folder 1)
  - "Bio"; Ray Benson resumes, Asleep at the Wheel list of awards and nominations, press biography, proof of entry for Ray Benson into the International Who's Who In Music – Volume 2: Popular Music, edited by Sophie Mason, 1 Asleep at the Wheel holiday card, 1972-1995 (Box 3331, Folder 2)
  - "PRESS 1976"; Press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel from various newspapers, newsletters and magazines, club dates and tour itinerary (Box 3331, Folder 3)
  - "PRESS 1975"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music magazines including Rolling Stone and German publications, band bio and Harrah's booking schedule (Box 3331, Folder 4)
  - "PRESS 1978"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music magazines (Box 3331, Folder 5)
  - "PRESS 1979"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music magazines (Box 3331, Folder 6)
  - "PRESS 1981"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music magazines (Also news clippings covering the closing of Armadillo World Headquarters club in Austin, Texas) (Box 3331, Folder 7)
  - "PRESS 1986"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel, Ray Benson, Candye Kane, The Fabulous Thunderbirds, Chuck Berry, Deanna Bogart and Commander Cody from various newspapers and music magazines (Box 3331, Folder 8)
  - "PRESS 1987"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson and the Rock and Roll Summit Moscow Concert from various newspapers and music magazines. Also includes an invitation to "An Evening of Our American Musical Culture" hosted by Tammy Wynette and Rick Blackburn (Box 3331, Folder 9)
  - "PRESS 1988-1990"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson, Atlantic Records and Farm Aid IV from various newspapers and magazines including Country Music Magazine, Rolling Stone Austin-American Statesman, Chicago Tribune and The Saint Louis Post- Dispatch (Box 3331, Folder 10)
  - "PRESS 1991"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel, Ray Benson and Dolly Parton from various newspapers and magazines including Vanity Fair, 1991. Majority of press features the NBC television movie Big T. co-starring Dolly Parton, Ray Benson and Gary Busey (Box 3331, Folder 11)
  - "PRESS 1992"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel, Ray Benson, Dolly Parton and The 66th Anniversary of Route 66 tour from various newspapers and magazines (Box 3331, Folder 12)
  - "Route 66 (1992)"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to The 66th Anniversary of Route 66, Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various magazines including Country America and newspapers (Box 3331, Folder 13)
  - "PRESS 1993"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to the album "Asleep at the Wheel: Tribute to the Music of Bob Wills and the Texas Playboys" produced by Ray Benson at Bismeaux Studios from various magazines and newspapers including USA Today, Musician, Country Song,That's Country, and The Journal of American Academy for the Preservation of Old Time Country Music (Box 3331, Folder 14)
  - "Press – No Date"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music magazines, 1993 (Box 3331, Folder 15)
  - "PRESS 1973"; Articles and press pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson, Commander Cody, and Hank Thomas from various newspapers and music magazines (Box 3331, Folder 16)
  - "PRESS 1972"; Washington Post and ZigZag magazine articles pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson (Box 3331, Folder 17)
  - "PRESS 1973-75"; Articles, press clippings and Capitol Records correspondence pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel, Ray Benson and Rusty Weir from various newspapers and newsletters, 1973-1975 (Box 3331, Folder 18)
  - "PRESS 1977"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers, magazine and trade releases including the San Francisco Chronicle, Country Music and Creem magazines and Capitol Records, 1973, 1977 (Box 3331, Folder 19)
  - "PRESS 1980"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers, and MCA Records (Box 3332, Folder 1)
  - "PRESS 1982"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including the Austin American Statesman, The Tennessean, The Pittsburg Press and the Philadelphia Inquirer, 1980-1987 (Box 3332, Folder 2)
  - "PRESS 1983"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including Amarillo Daily News, Kansas City Star, and Billboard, 1982-1988 (Box 3332, Folder 3)
  - "PRESS 1984"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including The Knoxville News-Sentinel, Austin American Statesman, and the Academy of Country Music (Box 3332, Folder 4)
  - "PRESS 1985"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines (Box 3332, Folder 5)
  - "PRESS 1991 Folder 2"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines. Majority of clippings relate to the NBC television premiere of the movie Wild Texas Rose starring Dolly Parton, Ray Benson and Gary Busey (Box 3332, Folder 6)
  - "PRESS 1994"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including Musician, Country Music, Billboard, American Cowboy, Country Weekly. Majority of press are reviews of the Bob Wills Tribute album Asleep at the Wheel Tribute to the Music of Bob Wills and The Texas Playboys and Grammy nominations for Asleep at the Wheel and Billboard charting of the Bob Wills tribute album, 1994-1995 (Box 3332, Folder 7)
  - "PRESS 1994 Folder no. 2"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including Rolling Stone and American Cowboy. Majority of press are reviews of the Bob Wills Tribute album Asleep at the Wheel Tribute to the Music of Bob Wills and The Texas Playboys and Grammy nominations for Asleep at the Wheel (Box 3332, Folder 8)
  - "PRESS 1995"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel Ray Benson and Austin City Limits 20th TV season from various newspapers and music trade magazines including the Austin American Statesman, Tennessean, Texas Monthly, Music City News, New Country and The Hollywood Reporter (Box 3332, Folder 9)
  - "PRESS 1997"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson (Box 3332, Folder 10)
  - "PRESS 1996"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers, newsletters and music trade magazines including Austin American Statesman, People, Music City News, New Country and Country Music (Box 3332, Folder 11)
  - "PRESS 1995 (Magazines)"; Articles and press clippings pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines including New Country, Fort Worth Star and USA Today (Box 3332, Folder 12)
  - "AATW Press 2004"; Articles, press clippings and correspondence pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and music trade magazines. Majority of press pertains to Asleep at the Wheel's album Asleep at the Wheel Remembers the Alamo and the movie The Alamo co-starring Billy Bob Thornton (Box 3332, Folder 13)
  - "Press 2006/2007"; Articles, press clippings and album reviews pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers, newsletters, music trade magazines both online outlets and print (Box 3332, Folder 14)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1987"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard album chart listings, album reviews, radio station rotation lists and correspondence pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines. Includes Asleep at the Wheel's CMA nomination for Vocal Group of the Year (Box 3332, Folder 15)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1987"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard album chart listings, album reviews pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines, 1987. Includes Asleep at the Wheel's CMA nomination for Vocal Group of the Year (Box 3333, Folder 1)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1988"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard album chart listings, album reviews and correspondence pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines, 1988-1989. Includes press relating to Asleep at the Wheel's Best Country Instrumental Grammy award for "String of Pars" from their album 10. File 1 of 2 (Box 3333, Folder 2)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1988"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard album chart listings, album reviews and correspondence pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines. Includes press relating to Asleep at the Wheel's Best Country Instrumental Grammy award for "String of Pars" from their album 10, 1988-1989 (Box 3333, Folder 3)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1989"; Drawings articles, press clippings, Billboard chart listings, album reviews and radio station chart lists pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines (national and international Includes press relating to Asleep at the Wheel's Best Country Instrumental Grammy nomination for "Sugarfoot Rag". File 1 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box 3333, Folder 4)
  - "Asleep at the Wheel Press 1989"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard chart listings, album reviews and radio station chart lists pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines (national and international. Includes press relating to Asleep at the Wheel's Best Country Instrumental Grammy nomination for "Sugarfoot Rag". File 2 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box 3333, Folder 5)
  - "2000 + Random Old"; Articles, press clippings, Billboard chart listings, album reviews pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines Includes press related to Asleep at the Wheel's Bob Wills tribute album A Ride with Bob and the band's 6 Grammy nominations for 2006, 1992-2006 (Box 3333, Folder 6)
  - "A Ride With Bob Press 2005"; Articles, press clippings, correspondence and reviews from various newspapers, newsletters and magazines both print and online pertaining to the play A Ride With Bob: from Austin to Tulsa written by Ray Benson and Anne Rapp, 2004-2005 (Box 3333, Folder 7)
  - "AATW Forget-Me-Nots: Posters and Flyers"; Correspondence to/from and about Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel, Stoney Plain (RCA) record catalog, bios, news clippings "AATW Forget-Me-Nots: Posters and Flyers"; Correspondence to/from and about Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel, Stoney Plain (RCA) record catalog, bios, news clippings Includes 1976 CMA Seminar proceedings and 1979 Grammy winner list., 1976-1995 (Box 3333, Folder 8)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Ray Benson product endorsements for Golfsmith golf clubs and Samick guitars, Homespun Tapes instructional video catalog which includes guitar instructional tape with Ray Benson, 1994-1996 (Box 3333, Folder 9)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Award certificates including The Academy Of Western Artists Will Rogers Cowboy Award, Western Swing Society Hall of Fame, Country Music Association Instrumental Group of the Year finalist, True West Best Living Western Music Group presented to Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel, 1979-2018 (Box 3333, Folder 10)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Regional performing arts programs including The Kennedy Center Texas Festival, University of Texas, Austin, and the Maine Center for the Performing Arts, Melody Fair Theater, 1991-1993, undated (Box 3333, Folder 11)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Music festival programs including the Long Beach Blues Festival, Philadelphia Jam on the River and the Singer-Songwriter Festival Frutigen Switzerland, 1990-1996 (Box 3333, Folder 12)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Funeral service program for Eugene "Gene" Ramey, December 13, 1984 (Box 3333, Folder 13)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Vince Gill Celebrity Basketball Game and Concert programs, 1992-1996 (Box 3333, Folder 14)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Photographs of Ray Benson and Asleep at the Wheel, 1993, undated (Box 3333, Folder 15)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Correspondence to Ray Benson, 1977-1988 (Box 3333, Folder 16)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Country Gold Music International Country Music Festival, Kumamoto, Japan itineraries, 1 copy of The Country: Japanese Country Music Magazine Vol.2, 1989-1990 (Box 3333, Folder 17)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; George Strait Chevy Truck Music Festival itinerary, Asleep at the Wheel long term itinerary, 1998, undated (Box 3333, Folder 18)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Asleep at the Wheel press kit materials, photos, bios, calendar. Includes 25th anniversary materials, 1975-1998 (Box 3333, Folder 19)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Asleep at the Wheel concert flyers, 1991, 1994, undated (Box 3333, Folder 20)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; As The Wheel Turns newsletters, Capitol International newsletter, Barton Creek Newsletter, ACM Country Focus newsletter, 1975, 1994-1998 (Box 3333, Folder 21)
  - "Old-Newsletters, Press kits, Photos"; Articles, press clippings and reviews pertaining to Asleep at the Wheel and Ray Benson from various newspapers and magazines including The New York Times, USA Today, Austin American Statesman, Philadelphia Inquirer, Washington Post, American Way, Country Weekly and Country Song, 1975-1997 (Box 3333, Folder 22)